staples-locator.com 2000-08-15

# Staples | Privacy Policy & Security

|  | >  | FAQs |   
---|---|---|---  
| >  | Site Map |   
| >  | Catalog Request |   
| >  | Privacy Policy & Security |   
|  |  |  |   
  
|  Customer Service /   
Privacy Policy & Security

Staples.com **Shopping Security** ensures that your credit card information is safe and your privacy respected. We protect your shopping experience by: 

  * utilizing SSL Technology 
  * hosting Our Site on Secure Servers 
  * maintaining [Secure Site status](https://digitalid.verisign.com/as2/f445076659f0c261bff312c765436536) from security industry leader VeriSign 
  * allowing you to opt out of any online or traditional telemarketing efforts 

We collect information so we can best meet your needs and notify you of offers that may be of interest. We firmly believe it's your right to know what information we collect, how we use it, and what your options are. Below you can find more detailed information about online security, information collection and use, and how to contact us. 

What Keeps My Credit Card Safe?   

At Staples.com, whenever you provide any personal information (e.g. when making a purchase, requesting a catalog, completing an e-mail form), we encrypt it so that no one can read it while it is being transmitted over the Internet. At this time, all information (such as your name and address) is safely stored behind a firewall. A firewall is a set of related programs that protects your information from users from other networks. We store this type of information so that you do not have to re-enter it each time you make a purchase or log in. 

Is My Personal Information Safe?   

Yes, any personal information that you submit to the site will remain safe and secure. In order to offer you an individualized shopping experience at Staples.com we collect various types of information such as: 

  * domain names of visitors to our Web site 
  * e-mail addresses of those who e-mail us or register with us 
  * information on how many visits each page receives 
  * user-specific information on what pages consumers visit 
  * information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations 

We then study this information to determine how we can create the best shopping experience available for you. By looking at usage patterns, we know which areas need expansion and which areas are not meeting your needs. We also collect information so that we can help you personalize the site, receive notice about special updates, and have access to unique marketing messages. 

How Can I Be Removed From Staples.com Lists?

E-mail  
If you do not want to receive e-mail about special offers from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an e-mail and telling us that you do not want to receive them from our company. 

Mail  
If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know in writing to:  

Staples  
500 Staples Drive  
Framingham, MA 01702  

Also, you may receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by writing to us at the above address. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations. 

Phone  
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online and/or current offers that may be of interest to them. You can reach us by telephone at:  

1-800-3STAPLE (1800-378-2753). 

|
